manausa.com 2008-12-18

# Tallahassee Real Estate Privacy Statement

### CENTURY 21 First Realty's Exclusive Privacy Policy

This privacy statement discloses the privacy practices for CENTURY 21 First Realty, ("Company"), Web site found on [www.manausa.com](http://www.manausa.com/).

This Web site has agreed to notify you of:

· What personally identifiable information of yours or third party personally identification is collected from you through the Web site

· The organization collecting the information

· How the information is used

· With whom the information may be shared

· What choices are available to you regarding collection, use and distribution of the information

· The kind of security procedures that are in place to protect the loss, misuse or alteration of information under the Company’s control

· How you can correct any inaccuracies in the information

If you feel that Company is not abiding by its posted privacy policy, you should first contact the Webmaster at [info@manausa.com](mailto:info@manausa.com). If you do not receive acknowledgment of your inquiry or your inquiry has not been satisfactorily addressed, you should then contact Joe Manausa at [joe@manausa.com](mailto:joe@manausa.com) to resolve your concerns.

1\. INFORMATION COLLECTION AND USE

Company is the sole owner of the information collected on this site. We will not sell, share, or rent this information to others in ways different from what is disclosed in this statement. Company collects information from our users at several different points on our Web site.

2\. REGISTRATION

In order to subscribe to this Web site's newsletter, a user must first complete the registration form. During registration a user is required to give their contact information (such as email address and optional name). This information is used to contact the user about the services on our site for which they have expressed interest.

3\. COOKIES

A cookie is a piece of data stored on the user’s hard drive containing non-contact information about the user. Cookies can also enable us to track and target the interests of our users to enhance the experience on our site. Usage of a cookie is in no way linked to any personally identifiable information while on our site. If a user rejects the cookie, they may still use our site. The only drawback to this is that the user may be limited in some areas of our site. Some of our business partners may use cookies on our site (for example, advertisers). However, we have no access to or control over these cookies.

4\. LOG FILES

We use IP addresses to analyze trends, administer the site, track user’s movement, and gather broad demographic information for aggregate use. IP addresses are not linked to personally identifiable information.

5\. SHARING

We will share aggregated demographic information with our partners and advertisers. This is not linked to any personal information that can identify any individual person. We partner from time to time with other parties to provide specific services. When the user signs up for these services, we will share names, or other contact information that is necessary for the third parties to provide these services. These parties are not allowed to use personally identifiable information except for the purpose of providing these services.

6\. LINKS

This web site contains links to other sites. Please be aware that Company is not responsible for the privacy practices of such other sites. We encourage our users to be aware when they leave our site and to read the privacy statements of each and every Web site that collects personally identifiable information. This Privacy Policy applies solely to information collected by this Web site.

7\. NEWSLETTER

If a user wishes to subscribe to our newsletter, we ask for contact information such as email address and optional name.

8\. SURVEYS AND CONTESTS

From time-to-time our site requests information from users via surveys or contests. Participation in these surveys or contests is completely voluntary and the user therefore has a choice whether or not to disclose this information. Information requested may include contact information (such as name and shipping address), and demographic information (such as zip code, age level). Contact information will be used to notify the winners and award prizes. Survey information will be used for purposes of monitoring or improving the use and satisfaction of this site and to provide a valuable educational experience to the survey participants.

9\. FORWARD TO A FRIEND

If a user elects to use our referral service for informing friends about our site or newsletter, we ask them for the friends' name and email address. Company or a third party service used by Company will automatically send the friends a one-time email inviting them to visit the site. This information is used for the sole purpose of sending this one-time email.

10\. CHOICE / OPT-OUT

Users who no longer wish to receive our newsletter may opt-out of receiving it by clicking the "Manage your subscription" link at the bottom of any Newsletter e-mail message.

11\. NOTIFICATION OF CHANGES

If we decide to change our Privacy Policy, we will post those changes this site's Homepage so our users are always aware of what information we collect, how we use it, and under which circumstances, if any, we disclose it. If at any point we decide to use personally identifiable information in a manner different from that stated at the time it was collected, we will notify users by way of an email. Users will have a choice as to whether or not we use their information in this different manner. We will use information in accordance with the privacy policy under which the information was collected.
